There are two sides to every crime.
I Know Who Killed Me is a thriller, horror, mystery
film directed by Chris Sivertson.
An idyllic small town is rocked when Aubrey Fleming, a bright and promising
young woman, is abducted and tortured by a sadistic serial killer.
When she manages to escape, the traumatized girl who regains consciousness in the hospital insists that she
is not who they think she is and that the real Aubrey Fleming is still in mortal danger.
Aubrey Fleming, played by Lindsay Lohan.
Susan Fleming, played by Julia Ormond.
Daniel Fleming, played by Neal McDonough.
Phil Lazarus, played by Spencer Garrett.
Dr. Greg Jameson, played by Gregory Itzin.
Jazmin, played by Kenya Moore.
I Know Who Killed Me is a 2007 American psychological thriller film
directed by Chris Sivertson from a screenplay by Jeff Hammond.
It stars Lindsay Lohan as a young woman who is abducted
and tortured by a sadistic serial killer.
After surviving the abduction, she insists that her
identity is that of another woman.
Julia Ormond, Neal McDonough, Brian Geraghty, Garcelle Beauvais, Spencer
Garrett and Bonnie Aarons appear in supporting roles.
The film received intense negative media coverage during production and upon its
release, as Lohan publicly struggled with addiction and other personal issues.
Filming took place mostly in California, from December 2006 to March 2007.
It was theatrically released in the United States by
TriStar Pictures on July 27, 2007.
It was promptly deemed a failure and called one of the worst films ever made, being the most
awarded at the 28th Golden Raspberry Awards, winning seven of eight nominations.
The film did, however, attain a more successful home video
performance, having almost quadrupled its U.S.
box office gross in estimated domestic DVD sales.
I Know Who Killed Me subsequently developed a cult following that has reexamined it as a modern giallo and
several screenings of it have been put together by historic theaters and film festivals.
The film explores themes of daughter, sadism, kidnapping, sadistic, striptease.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.